(Sheldon:)Never mind.
(Sheldon:)You know, Penny went to this spa
to be away from you.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure
you should be going there?
(Leonard:)I don't want to wait two days
for us to work this out.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)You got married
spur of the moment.
(Sheldon:)I don't see why your
divorce should be any different.
(Leonard:)I would pull this car over
and kick you out,
(Leonard:)but... if Penny dumps me,
you're all I got.
(Penny:)When was the last time
you got a massage?
(Amy:)Sheldon walked on my back
two weeks ago,
(Amy:)but that was just 'cause
there was a spider on his pillow
(Amy:)and he was trying to get away.
(Penny:)Leonard stood on me once, too,
(Penny:)but he was just trying
to see the Rose Parade.
(Amy:)I don't know the protocol,
(Amy:)are you gonna be naked
for your massage?
(Penny:)Well. Yeah.
(Amy:)Hmm. Then this is probably
too many clothes.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Penny:)What are you doing here?